pamperedpassions.com 2013-06-01

# Privacy Policy - Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie

This is the official web site of Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie, online at www.PamperedPassions.com, commited to the protection of customer information, confidentiality and privacy. 

**Mailing Address:**  
Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie  
9615 E County Line Road, Suite D   
Englewood, CO 80112 

**Email Address** :  
info@pamperedpassions.com

**Phone:**  
Toll Free USA: 1-888-775-4643 (1-888-PP-Lingerie)

**Shop online at www.PamperedPassions.com with confidence.**

Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie is one of the largest retailers of lingerie in the world, with retail distribution through brick and mortar stores, direct mail catalogs and secure websites. We import fine lingerie from around the world to offer one of the most diverse product offerings online. Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie sells lingerie to over 50 countries world wide and has been awarded the Best Lingerie Store in the USA by the Intima Group for our customer service, communication and diverse product selection. 

Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie is just as concerned about credit card fraud as our customers are concerned about fraudulent and questionable businesses online. Therefore, to protect our customers, we have have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to offer safe and secure credit card transactions for our customers.

The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the credit card and electronic check processing networks. The company adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including: 

  * 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions. 

  * Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information. 

  * Compliance with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standard.

For additional information regarding the privacy of your sensitive cardholder data, please read the Authorize.Net Privacy Policy ( _http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy)._

**www.pamperedpassions.com is registered with the Authorize.Net Secure Payments Seal program.**

**COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION:**

NO INFORMATION IS SHARED NOR SOLD, ALL INFORMATION IS CONFIDENTIAL. 

OUR SHOPPING CART IS 100% PCI COMPLIANT - WE DO NOT HOLD CREDIT CARD INFORMATION.   
(most shopping carts store, or retain, customer credit card information in their server's database, thus, exposing your credit card information to potential access) 

Upon visiting www.PamperedPassions.com, our server will automatically recognize the visiting computer's ip address and service provider.

Visitors who supply us information pertaining to name, address, telephone number and email address may be contacted to provide information regarding an order and other information pertaining to PamperedPassions.com. 

Information we collect will never be sold to third parties and is used to improve the content of our website, process orders, respond to customer inquiries and to provide a more satisfying shopping experience. By using PamperedPassions.com, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie.

**  
EMAIL ADDRESS:**

Email addresses collected at PamperedPassions.com are never sold nor shared with any third party.

Email addresses will be stored to allow for prompt communication of information via email pertaining to the status of an order as well as to provide information, promotions, events and updates. By electing to receive emails from Pampered Passions, we are able to send you exclusive information and special offers, which you might otherwise not be informed. Follow the UNSUBSCRIBE link located at the bottom of each email to stop receiving them. Requesting removal will not prevent you from receiving emails regarding the status of an order. 

If you would prefer not to receive email regarding special offers and discounts, send an email to info@pamperedpassions.com with “ **Unsubscribe Special Offers** ” in the subject line.   

**PERSONAL INFORMATION:**

No personal information is sold nor shared with any third party. Credit card information is NOT stored nor retained.

Address, email and telephone information may be used to contact the customer regarding the status of an order or to provide information from Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie. Should you wish to avoid communication by any method, please send an email to info@pamperedpassions.com with the subject line: "NO PHONE CALLS", "NO EMAILS", and/or "NO POSTAL MAIL". 

_We do not store any payment information and are 100% PCI compliant. Most online stores are not, which means they likely store your credit card information and, subsequently, leave it vulnerable to access and abuse._

We reserves the right to disclose personal information as obligated by law, in response to duly authorized legal process, governmental requests and as necessary to protect the rights and interests of Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie.   

**USE OF THIRD PARTIES:**

We use third parties to help us provide services to you including such things as fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, conducting surveys, maintaining our database, administering emails, and administering drawings or contests, and to provide aggregate, comparative information on the performance of our site to us and a select group. Information will be shared with these third parties only to the extent necessary to provide these services. 

**USE OF COOKIES:**

We use cookies placed on your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser during your visit to our site and when you return to our site. For instance, when you are ready to purchase an item, a cookie allows our site to "remember" you have added the item to your shopping cart. We can also show you merchandise based on your preferences and provide you with a more personalized shopping experience. 

**CONDITIONS OF USE:**

PAMPERED PASSIONS FINE LINGERIE DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THIS SITE, ITS SERVERS, OR EMAIL SENT BY US OR ON OUR BEHALF ARE VIRUS FREE. PAMPERED PASSIONS WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO COMPENSATORY, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, LOSS OF DATA, GOODWILL, BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY, INCOME OR PROFIT, LOSS OF OR DAMAGE TO PROPERTY AND CLAIMS OF THIRD PARTIES. IN NO EVENT WILL PAMPERED PASSIONS FINE LINGERIE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER IN AN AMOUNT IN EXCESS OF ANY PURCHASED MADE HEREUNDER AND IF NO PURCHASE IS MADE, IN AN AMOUNT IN EXCESS OF TWENTY FIVE DOLLARS. 

CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS, OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS. 

**APPLICABLE LAW:**

By visiting this site, you agree that the laws of the State of Colorado, without regard to its conflict of laws principles, govern this privacy policy and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Pampered Passions or its affiliates. We participate in the Better Business Bureau's BBBOnLine Program. This means that we have committed to cooperating with BBB efforts to resolve disputes that may arise under this contract. Upon your request, we will agree to participate in a BBB dispute resolution process to resolve these disputes. There are limits as to the kinds of claims that the BBB will handle -- call the BBB for more information. Other than for those disputes resolved through the BBB dispute resolution process, you consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in the courts of Colorado. 

**UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION:**

You may update or modify your contact information and user preferences by logging into "My Account".  

**LINKS:**

For your convenience, our website may contain links to other sites. Pampered Passions Fine Lingerie is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.   

**SECURITY STATEMENT:**

Our site only accepts orders from Web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, which encrypts information you input. This means you should not be able to inadvertently place an order through an unsecured connection. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. While we implement the above security measures on this site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm.

This privacy statement is effective as of October 1st, 2011.
